Lloyd: Hi.
In this Time to Think video, I'm
going to demonstrate the purpose of
the Time to Think boxes that you will
encounter throughout the course and
how they can assist you when you come
to complete your assessment questions.
So as you can see, I'm currently on
page one of session one of unit one.
And if I scroll down, you can see
there's some useful information relating
to the different topics that you will
cover; the different icons that you
will encounter as you work through.
And by clicking on those, it will
explain what each of those icons is.
There are also a couple of videos
relating to submitting assessments,
this video -- the Time to Think.
And then if I click on page two, this
page contains information relating
to your learning goals and some goal
setting information and also some
hints and tips that relate to unit one.
Each of the units has their own hints
and tips, which you can download
from page one of each of the units.
And then on page three, you
then come to the actual content
relating to understanding coding.
So as you can see, scroll down
there, there are various elements.
There's videos, there's things
to read, sliders, there are
quizzes, there are read items.
And then on page four, there's
further information relating to
the types of language, syntax
and technologies and more videos.
And then, as you come to the
bottom of page four, you will
see there is a Time to Think box.
These Time to Think boxes are designed
to make you think and generate ideas
that will assist you when you come
to answer the assessment questions.
So this very first Time to Think
is asking what items in your home
do you think uses code to run?
So what are the different devices
in your home that would need to
have code within them to operate?
I'll just put TV in there.
And if I click save, that is
then being saved to my journal.
So as you work through the course, each
of the different sessions and each of
the units, you will encounter a number
of Time to Thinks and they do relate
directly to the assessment questions.
So, there's another Time to Think there,
and if I just type in there, this one
is asking that now that I've watched
the video, have a think about the
roles and why teamworking is important.
I'll just type "test" in there,
click save, and again, the
journal entry has been saved.
So how do I access that?
So if I go back to the top and
click on My Course, and then I look
at the top, I can see my Journal.
If I click on my journal icon, I can see
there that on the 27th, these are the
entries that I've made into my journal.
And it's unit one, session one, page four.
Unit one, session two, page two.
And as you can see the information
that I have typed into the Time
to Think box has been saved.
So when you come to do the actual
questions in the assessment, you
can refer back to your journal.
There's a little calendar at the top
there, which will have a tick next to
it, which will indicate that information
has been entered on that date and
then you can scroll down through the
information that you've saved and
find that information, and hopefully
that can assist you when you come to
complete your assessment questions.